Bruno Kazadi

Computer Science Student

Contact

Address

Gloucester, ON K1V 8Y6

Phone

8736641966

E-mail

kbrunojr55@gmail.com

www

https://bold.pro/my/brunokazadi/465

Technical Profile

- Python
- Microsoft Office
- HTML
- SQL
- JavaScript
- Java
- CSS
- MySQL
- Git
- React
- Go
- PostgreSQL
- Flask
- Bootstrap
- Visual Studio Code
- Spring Boot
- Docker
- Kubernetes

Enthusiastically committed to solving challenges using computer science techniques, I have gained experience working with a wide array of technologies. My constant drive to learn and adapt to new technologies reflects my inquisitive nature. I find fulfillment in working on hard problems and excel as a collaborative team member. My passion is fueled by the profound impact technology continues to make on the world.

Work History

2022-05 -2022-09

Junior programmer

Grand-B Technologies

- Designed and coded 50+ unit and integration testing
- Troubleshooted 50+ code-related issues and defects
- Produced detailed design documentation, unit test plans, and documented code
- Practiced strong configuration management and version control for 4 projects

2021-11 -2022-04

Telemarketing Representative

PL-Telecom, Gatineau, Quebec

- Maintaining database by entering, verifying, and backing up data
- Documenting transactions by completing forms and record logs
- Advising present or prospective customers by answering incoming calls on a rotating basis
- Keeping equipment operational by following manufacturer's instructions and establishing procedures; notifying team leader of needed repairs
- Maintaining technical knowledge by attending educational workshops; reviewing publications

PROJECTS

Web Development And More

- Built a Home-made monitoring system with Raspberry Pi and microservices Using Java and Go
- Built features using scikit-learn in Python that learned what time of day maximized engagement with social media posts and increased the overall user

Competencies

Go

Java

HTML/ CSS

Python

SQL

REST APIs

Git/GitHub

Spring boot

React.js

Javascript

Postgres

Clean Architecture

Kubernetes

Docker

AWS

Excellent Communication

Problem-Solving

Data analysis

Computer networking

- engagement rate by 15%
- Built a full-stack Go web application called "Snippetbox" that lets users CRUD text snippets (similar to GitHub gists).
- A course booking android app using java and android studio.
- Design and development of a production grade enterprise (Dental Clinic) management system using Spring Boot.
- Web Scraper using the Twitter and Instagram API's
- Currently building a scalable production grade sales-API in Go leveraging the power of Kubernetes.

Education

2020-09 *-*2024-07 **B.S: Computer Science and Mathematics**

University of Ottawa - Ottawa, Ontario